Guide to the Cross & Brown Company Architectural Photograph Collection [1970]-1991 PR 111
@ 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Negatives
  - Manhattan Properties
    - 230 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 386)
    - 270 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 387)
    - 280 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 388)
    - 300 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 389)
    - 320 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 390)
    - 345 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 391)
    - 390 Park Avenue (Lever House) (Box 7, Folder 392)
    - 400 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 393)
    - 405 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 394)
    - 410 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 395)
    - 425-430 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 396)
    - 460 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 397)
    - 475 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 398)
    - 499 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 399)
    - 505 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 400)
    - 1443 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 401)
    - Miscellaneous - Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 402)
    - 1-2 Penn Plaza (Box 7, Folder 403)
    - 80 Pine Street (Box 7, Folder 404)
    - 19 Rector Street (Box 7, Folder 405)
    - Rockefeller Ceneter (Box 7, Folder 406)
    - 1 State Street Plaza (American Express Plaza) (Box 7, Folder 407)
    - 37 Wall Street (Box 7, Folder 408)
    - 40 Wall Street (Box 7, Folder 409)
    - 45 Wall Street (Box 7, Folder 410)
    - 55 Wall Street (Box 7, Folder 411)
    - 60 Wall Street (Box 7, Folder 412)
    - 63 Wall Street (Box 7, Folder 413)
    - 100 Wall Street (Box 7, Folder 414)
    - 111 Wall Street (Box 7, Folder 415)
    - 1 Water Street (Box 7, Folder 416)
    - 55 Water Street (Box 7, Folder 417)
    - 77 Water Street (Box 7, Folder 418)
    - 160 Water Street (Box 7, Folder 419)
    - 90 William Street (Box 7, Folder 420)
    - 100 William Street (Box 7, Folder 421)
    - 110 William Street (Box 7, Folder 422)
    - 150 William Street (Box 7, Folder 423)
    - 161 William Street (Box 7, Folder 424)
    - World Trade Center (Box 7, Folder 425)
    - 815 Second Avenue (Box 7, Folder 426)
    - 866 Second Avenue (Box 7, Folder 427)
    - Miscellaneous - Second Avenue (Box 7, Folder 428)
    - 600 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 429)
    - 605 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 430)
    - 630 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 431)
    - 711Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 432)
    - 747 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 433)
    - 767 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 434)
    - 780 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 435)
    - 800 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 436)
    - 805 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 437)
    - 825 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 438)
    - 850 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 439)
    - 866 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 440)
    - 875 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 441)
    - 900 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 442)
    - 909 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 443)
    - 919 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 444)
    - 964 Third Avenue (Box 7, Folder 445)
    - 122 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 446)
    - 241 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 447)
    - 347 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 448)
    - 518 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 449)
    - 522 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 450)
    - 530 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 451)
    - 551 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 452)
    - 555 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 453)
    - 575 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 454)
    - 592 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 455)
    - 600 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 456)
    - 640 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 457)
    - 665 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 458)
    - 666 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 459)
    - 717 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 460)
    - 725 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 461)
    - 767 Fifth Avenue (General Motors Building) (Box 8, Folder 462)
    - 768 Fifth Avenue (Plaza Hotel) (Box 8, Folder 463)
    - 1045 Sixth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 464)
    - 1114 Sixth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 465)
    - 1155 Sixth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 466)
    - 1166 Sixth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 467)
    - 1185 Sixth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 468)
    - 1230 Sixth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 469)
    - 1285 Sixth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 470)
    - 1290 Sixth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 471)
    - 1345 Sixth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 472)
    - 1350 Sixth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 473)
    - 398 Seventh Avenue (Box 8, Folder 474)
    - 729 Seventh Avenue (Box 8, Folder 475)
    - 767 Seventh Avenue (Equitable Building) (Box 8, Folder 476)
    - 810 Seventh Avenue (Box 8, Folder 477)
    - 888 Seventh Avenue (Box 8, Folder 478)
    - 441 Ninth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 479)
    - 150 East 3rd Street (Box 8, Folder 480)
    - 227 West 22nd Street (Box 8, Folder 481)
    - 43 West 23rd Street (Box 8, Folder 482)
    - 15-19 East 26th Street (Box 8, Folder 483)
    - East 32nd Street (Box 8, Folder 484)
    - 450 East 33rd Street (Box 8, Folder 485)
    - 22 East 38th Street (Lancaster Hotel) (Box 8, Folder 486)
    - 25 West 39th Street (Box 8, Folder 487)
    - 8 East 40th Street (Box 8, Folder 488)
    - 10 East 40th Street (Box 8, Folder 489)
    - 21 East 40th Street (Box 8, Folder 490)
    - 12 East 41st Street (Box 8, Folder 491)
    - 5 East 42nd Street (Box 8, Folder 492)
    - 100 East 42nd Street (Box 8, Folder 493)
    - 200 East 42nd Street (Box 8, Folder 494)
    - 235 East 42nd Street (Box 8, Folder 495)
    - 300 East 42nd Street (Box 8, Folder 496)
    - 11 East 44th Street (Box 8, Folder 497)
    - 144 East 42nd Street (Box 8, Folder 498)
    - 8-10 East 45th Street (Box 8, Folder 499)
    - 140 East 45th Street (Grand Central Tower) (Box 8, Folder 500)
    - 5 West 45th Street (Charette) (Box 8, Folder 501)
    - 20 East 46th Street (Box 8, Folder 502)
    - 3 West 46th Street (Box 8, Folder 503)
    - 43 West 46th Street (Box 8, Folder 504)
    - 12 East 48th Street (Box 8, Folder 505)
    - 16 East 48th Street (Box 8, Folder 506)
    - 11-17 East 49th Street (Box 8, Folder 507)
    - 50th Street and Lexington Avenue (Box 8, Folder 508)
    - 34 East 51st Street (Box 8, Folder 509)
    - 15 West 51st Street (Box 8, Folder 510)
    - 150 East 52nd Street (Box 8, Folder 511)
    - 10 East 53rd Street (Box 8, Folder 512)
    - 39 West 55th Street (Box 8, Folder 513)
    - 126 East 56th Street (Box 8, Folder 514)
    - 155 East 56th Street (Box 8, Folder 515)
    - 165 East 56th Street (Box 8, Folder 516)
    - 3 West 57th Street (Box 8, Folder 517)
    - 111 West 57th Street (Box 8, Folder 518)
    - 555 West 57th Street (Box 8, Folder 519)
    - 304 East 58th Street (Box 9, Folder 520)
    - 4 West 48th Street (Box 9, Folder 521)
    - West 59th Street (St. Moritz Hotel) (Box 9, Folder 522)
    - 45 East 62nd Street (Box 9, Folder 523)
    - 200 East 62nd Street (Box 9, Folder 524)
    - 500 East 62nd Street (Box 9, Folder 525)
    - 39 East 63rd Street (Box 9, Folder 526)
    - 2 East 86th Street (Box 9, Folder 527)
    - 12 East 86th Street (Box 9, Folder 528)
    - Skyviews (Box 9, Folder 529)
  - New York State Properties
    - Brewster - 30-50 Main Street (Putnam Terrace Apartments) (Box 9, Folder 530)
    - Brooklyn - 1025 Atlantic Avenue (Spiral Screw Building) (Box 9, Folder 531)
    - Brooklyn - 380 Henry Street (Box 9, Folder 532)
    - Brooklyn - 184 Kent Avenue (Box 9, Folder 533)
    - Brooklyn - 1248 Ralph Avenue (Box 9, Folder 534)
    - Brooklyn - 470 Vanderbilt Avenue (Box 9, Folder 535)
    - Brooklyn - Pan-Metal Products, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 536)
    - The Bronx - Bruckner Blvd. (TSS Plaza) (Box 9, Folder 537)
    - The Bronx - City Island (Box 9, Folder 538)
    - Carmel - Kent Shopping Center (Box 9, Folder 539)
    - Elmsford - 33 West Tarrytown Road (Crossroads Office Building) (Box 9, Folder 540)
    - Garden City - Avis World Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 541)
    - Germantown - Palatine Park Plaza (Box 9, Folder 542)
    - Harrison - 83 Calvert Street (Box 9, Folder 543)
    - Haverstraw - Florham Park (Box 9, Folder 544)
    - Lynbrook - 444 Merrick Road (Box 9, Folder 545)
    - Patterson - Robin Hill Corp. Park (Box 9, Folder 546)
    - Port Chester - One Gateway Plaza (Village Savings Bank) (Box 9, Folder 547)
    - Queens - 115-58 Don Kirk Street (Home Care Products Inc.) (Box 9, Folder 548)
    - Queens - 2100 Hunters Point (Hunters Point Plaza) (Box 9, Folder 549)
    - Queens - Long Island City (Manhattan Industries) (Box 9, Folder 550)
    - Queens - Newtown Creek, Long Island City (Daily News Building) (Box 9, Folder 551)
    - Queens - 32-75 Steinway Street, Long Island City (Box 9, Folder 552)
    - Queens - 54-35 46th Street, Maspeth (Box 9, Folder 553)
    - 19-03 75th Street, Astoria (Box 9, Folder 554)
    - Somers - Route 100 (Kipp Property) (Box 9, Folder 555)
    - Southampton (Box 9, Folder 556)
    - Suffern - 75 Montebello Road, Montebello Park (Thomas Fortune Ryan estate) (Box 9, Folder 557)
    - Tappan - Tappan Elementary School Condominiums (Box 9, Folder 558)
    - Verona (Box 9, Folder 559)
    - White Plains - 150 Grand Street (Box 9, Folder 560)
    - White Plains - 811 North Broadway (Medical Arts Building) (Box 9, Folder 561)
    - White Plains - 178 South Fulton Avenue (Box 9, Folder 562)
    - White Plains - 179 Westmoreland Avenue (Box 9, Folder 563)
    - White Plains - White Swan Restaurant (Box 9, Folder 564)
    - White Plains - Skyviews (Box 9, Folder 565)
    - White Plains - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 566)
    - Yonkers - 167 Saw Mill River Road (Box 9, Folder 567)
    - Unidentified - Putnam County (Box 9, Folder 568)
  - Cross & Brown Company
    - Employees (Box 9, Folder 569)
    - Seminars and meetings (Box 9, Folder 570-575)
- Series III: Slides
  Series III consists entirely slides of Manhattan buildings, arranged by address, dating predominantly from the 1980s.
  - 2 Dag Hammerskjold Plaza (Box 10)
  - 270 Lafayette Street (Box 10)
  - 345 Madison Avenue (Box 10)
  - 575 Madison Avenue (Box 10)
  - Park Avenue - Park Avenue Plaza (Box 10)
  - 200 Park Avenue (Box 10)
  - 1443 Park Avenue (Box 10)
  - 63 Wall Street (Box 10)
  - 800 Third Avenue (Box 10)
  - 729 Seventh Avenue (Box 10)
- Series IV: Documents
  Series IV consists of a variety of documents relating to buildings depicted in Series I through III. Most of the materials were created to be used in conjunction with photographs in Cross & Brown Company's brochures and other promotional materials; both finished and rough copies of these brochures are available in this series. The series is arranged by Manhattan address, with named streets filed alphabetically followed by numbered avenues and numbered streets. A list of exclusive agency listings for 1980, 1984, and 1985 is filed at the end of the series.
  - 335 Madison Avenue (Box 11, Folder 576)
  - 535 Madison Avenue (Box 11, Folder 577)
  - 540 Madison Avenue (Box 11, Folder 578)
  - 200 Park Avenue (Box 11, Folder 579)
  - 405 Park Avenue (Box 11, Folder 580)
  - 475 Park Avenue (Box 11, Folder 581)
  - 45 Wall Street (Box 11, Folder 582)
  - 729 Seventh Avenue (Box 11, Folder 583)
  - 450 East 33rd Street (Box 11, Folder 584)
  - 150 East 52nd Street (Box 11, Folder 585)
  - Exclusive Agency Listings, 1980, 1984, and 1985 (Box 11, Folder 586)